export const questions = [
    {
        question: "Q1) What is the Capital of India ?",
        OptionA: "Panaji",
        OptionB: "Bihar",
        OptionC: "Delhi",
        OptionD: "Chennai",
        Answer: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "Q2) What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
        OptionA: "Earth",
        OptionB: "Mars",
        OptionC: "Jupiter",
        OptionD: "Venus",
        Answer: "C"
    },

    {
        question: "Q3) Which gas do plants absorb from the atmosphere during photosynthesis?",
        OptionA: "Oxygen",
        OptionB: "Carbon dioxide",
        OptionC: "Nitrogen",
        OptionD: "Hydrogen",
        Answer: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Q4) Who is the author of the Harry Potter book series?",
        OptionA: "J.R.R. Tolkien",
        OptionB: "J.K. Rowling",
        OptionC: "George Orwell",
        OptionD: "Stephen King",
        Answer: "B"
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Q5) Which country is known as the Land of the Rising Sun?",
        OptionA: "China",
        OptionB: "South Korea",
        OptionC: "Japan",
        OptionD: "Thailand",
        Answer: "C"
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Q6) What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
        OptionA: "Au",
        OptionB: "Ag",
        OptionC: "Fe",
        OptionD: "Hg",
        Answer: "A"
    }
    ,

    {
        question: "Q7) Which gas is most abundant in Earth's atmosphere?",
        OptionA: "Oxygen",
        OptionB: "Nitrogen",
        OptionC: "Carbon dioxide",
        OptionD: "Hydrogen",
        Answer: "B"
    },
    {
        question: "Q8) Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
        OptionA: "Pablo Picasso",
        OptionB: "Vincent van Gogh",
        OptionC: "Leonardo da Vinci",
        OptionD: "Salvador Dali",
        Answer: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "Q9) Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
        OptionA: "Earth",
        OptionB: "Mars",
        OptionC: "Venus",
        OptionD: "Jupiter",
        Answer: "B"
    },
    {
        question: "Q10) What is the largest mammal in the world?",
        OptionA: "Elephant",
        OptionB: "Giraffe",
        OptionC: "Blue whale",
        OptionD: "Kangaroo",
        Answer: "C"
    }
]

